<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Risk on Betting On Success</title>
    <link>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/tags/risk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Risk on Betting On Success</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>MIT License</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 09:45:26 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/tags/risk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Risk is your Best Friend</title>
      <link>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/risk-is-your-best-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 09:45:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/risk-is-your-best-friend/</guid>
      <description>Risk is the intentional interaction with uncertainty. Humans by nature do not like uncertainty. We like to know how what to expect. This quote from Heath Ledger&amp;rsquo;s portrayal of the Joker is telling “Nobody panics when things go “according to plan”. Even if the plan is horrifying!”. So we love order even if it is bad events that are in order.
So why is Risk our Friend?
Risk is the interaction with uncertainty and if we can handle even a little bit of uncertainty we can be certain we are doing the right thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going All-In</title>
      <link>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/going-all-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:29:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/going-all-in/</guid>
      <description>Today I took my first step towards achieving my dreams, I quit my job! This has been a plan of mine for a long time and I have multiple contingency plans in place. Pursuing my side hustle has been a dream of mine for over 4 years now. I am now finally making it a reality! It is both exciting as well as frightening.
I am able to leave a high paying stable IT job because I have been saving a large percentage of my income regularly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Ruin</title>
      <link>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/risk-of-ruin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2001 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/risk-of-ruin/</guid>
      <description>This blog is titled Betting On Success, so you might think I am focusing on the success, which I am but I also give due importance (but no more) to failure. I focus on success because humans are naturally overly risk adverse and tend to weight loses twice as much as wins. Humans are naturally risk adverse.
 &amp;ldquo;Risk aversion is a preference for a sure outcome over a gamble with higher or equal expected value.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>