<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Betting On Success</title>
    <link>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Betting On Success</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>MIT License</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 09:45:26 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Risk is your Best Friend</title>
      <link>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/risk-is-your-best-friend/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 09:45:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/risk-is-your-best-friend/</guid>
      <description>Risk is the intentional interaction with uncertainty. Humans by nature do not like uncertainty. We like to know how what to expect. This quote from Heath Ledger&amp;rsquo;s portrayal of the Joker is telling “Nobody panics when things go “according to plan”. Even if the plan is horrifying!”. So we love order even if it is bad events that are in order.
So why is Risk our Friend?
Risk is the interaction with uncertainty and if we can handle even a little bit of uncertainty we can be certain we are doing the right thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doubling Down</title>
      <link>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/doubling-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 06:39:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/doubling-down/</guid>
      <description>Doubling Down is a move in Blackjack where you can double your original bet when you have a good hand so you can make even more money. I feel like this is a fitting post. In 2018, Mr and Mrs. BoS are Doubling Down on a some things while quitting others.
Removing
 Selling Fix and Flip that is currently rented Finishing 3+ year IT contract job Other investments etc  Doubling Down</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WATER on FIRE</title>
      <link>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/water-on-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 19:30:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/water-on-fire/</guid>
      <description>As we all know in the FIRE community, FI/RE stands for Financial Independence / Retire Early. I want to be so bold as to attempt to introduce a new acronym into our FIRE vocabulary, WATER.
Putting WATER on FIRE might sound contradictory but if we separate Water, H20, into individual parts we get Hydrogen and Oxygen which burns quite well; I find the same for the WATER acronym.
So let&amp;rsquo;s get into it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investing vs Gambling</title>
      <link>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/investing-vs-gambling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/investing-vs-gambling/</guid>
      <description>Being tax season I thought it would be fitting to discuss a heavy but important subject that I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen discussed in the FIRE community or much at all online though ironically in the professional gambling world it has. I want to frame it in the context of FIRE.
Investing vs Gambling. What is the difference? Say you&amp;rsquo;re sitting at the dinner table with family and you say &amp;ldquo;I just bought a share of Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s stock last year, I sold it and made $200&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forever Home</title>
      <link>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/dream-house-to-dream-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 01:58:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/dream-house-to-dream-life/</guid>
      <description>Fall 2016 my wife and I bought our forever home. This is a major life goal for us. This is where we want to stay essentially forever. We will travel all around the world but at the end always end up home. A large part of why we picked our specific home is that it gives us numerous activities to do once we are Financially Independent and have children. We could have easily stayed in our fix and flip house longer or bought a home for half the price; This home was worth it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quit My Job and Stayed</title>
      <link>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/quit-my-job-and-stayed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 17:05:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/quit-my-job-and-stayed/</guid>
      <description>My first post was about going ALL-IN and taking risks to achieve my dreams. Naturally, I assumed that meant going extreme and quitting my job, which I did the day of that post. What followed was quite unexpected; my job wouldn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;lsquo;let&amp;rsquo; me quit. Obviously they couldn&amp;rsquo;t literally keep me from quitting but they did everything that could to keep me from doing so. Frankly, I was shocked. I really do like the company and the direction they are going in but was, naturally, excited to pursue my crazy hobby as a professional.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going All-In</title>
      <link>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/going-all-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:29:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/going-all-in/</guid>
      <description>Today I took my first step towards achieving my dreams, I quit my job! This has been a plan of mine for a long time and I have multiple contingency plans in place. Pursuing my side hustle has been a dream of mine for over 4 years now. I am now finally making it a reality! It is both exciting as well as frightening.
I am able to leave a high paying stable IT job because I have been saving a large percentage of my income regularly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expected Value</title>
      <link>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/expected-value/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2001 09:27:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.bettingonsuccess.com/post/expected-value/</guid>
      <description>Expected Value This is another important Definition post where we&amp;rsquo;ll define a concept that we can then apply to investing. I will even give examples of how Expected Value (EV) can be applied each and every day.
So I think we all understand what Value is. We value $, time, family, or if you&amp;rsquo;re like me in the mornings sleep. Expectation is the act of looking toward the future and planning on something happening.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>